plus-model-mag.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - PLUS Model Magazine

_Updated 5/23/2018_  
****

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## Who we are

Our website address is: [https://www.plus-model-mag.com](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/)

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

This website utilizes Google Analytics to help us in understanding our audience so that we can develop content and experiences readers may enjoy. Google Analytics is a freemium web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic and data, which it stores for 26 months. You can view the [Google Privacy & Terms here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Compliancy Policy here](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/compliance/#?modal_active=none).

We may use the information we collect when you sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To send periodic email newsletters or other products and services.
  * To administer a giveaway, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To follow up with you after correspondence (email or phone inquiries).

### Newsletter

We collect your name and email address when signing up for our newsletter.

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### Giveaways and Surveys

With your express permission, we may collect information from you, like name, email and country. All terms of participation will be included with each giveaway or survey.

### Contact forms

We keep contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, or to follow up with you after correspondence, but we do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since all browsers are a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

We also use cookies to:

  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Personal data

### Who we share your data with

This website makes use of Google Analytics, which stores data for 26 months. You can view the [Google Privacy & Terms here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) and [Compliancy Policy here](https://privacy.google.com/businesses/compliance/#?modal_active=none).

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can [request to receive an exported file of the personal data](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/about-2/right-to-be-forgotten/) we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also [request that we erase any personal data](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/about-2/right-to-be-forgotten/) we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

 ** _Please[contact us here](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/about-2/contact/) for privacy-specific concerns._**

## Additional data information

### How we protect your data

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  If we are alerted to a security breech, you will be contacted via email within 48 hours.

### Third party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners, email management and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##  **Ad Management and Displays**

This website uses [Broadstreet Ads](https://broadstreetads.com/privacy-policy/), as well as [Google AdSense](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/1348695?hl=en).

 **Broadstreet** is an ad management platform that we use to manage client campaigns, advertisements, and ad delivery. Broadstreet does not collect personally identifiable information as part of the ad delivery process. It does not sell or share customer data or visitor data. For more information, view the [Privacy Policy here.](https://broadstreetads.com/privacy-policy/)

 **Google AdSense** is a program run by Google that allows publishers in the Google Network of content sites to serve automatic text, image, video, or interactive media advertisements, that are targeted to site content and audience. Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by [Google’s Advertising Principles](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en). They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

 **We have implemented the following:**

  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Settings page](https://adssettings.google.com/). Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)or by using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

## Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.  [See more here](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf)

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Our privacy policy is available from our home page, as well as our about page.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information, where applicable:

  *  _[By emailing us](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/about-2/contact/)_

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

### If there are any questions regarding these policies, you may contact us using the information below.

Publisher, [Venus Imaging Education, LLC](http://viethrive.com/)  
Vancouver, WA 98683  
USA  
Phone: 360-882-4416  
Email: [Click Here](https://www.plus-model-mag.com/about-2/contact/)
